As you've noticed, we aren't actually testing
that new function yet. Fortunately, we have a
pretty good spot in doing background to
do that. After all, right here we've already
parsed everything we need to call that function. So, we can just call long
locationId equals addLocation cityName locationQuery
citylatitude, and citylongitude. It would be useful for our contract to have
another method, one that converts a date object
to the format our database uses. Note that Android
Studio may have trouble importing this data object,
since Java has two day classes, one in databases,
and one in java.util. We want java.util.date. Back
in the FetchWeatherTask, we're going to collect the data
from JSON into the weather array. All right, so
we now have a whole bunch of data that
needs to be inserted. Guess what we're going to do next?